Star Wars Biomes is a science fiction, documentary film directed by None.
Take a virtual vacation to some of the Star Wars films' most iconic and beloved locations like Hoth, Tatooine, and
Sorgan, as this charming series whisks you off for fly-through tours of the Galaxy Far, Far Away.
The Star Wars franchise has spawned multiple films and television series.
Two animated series were released in the mid-1980s.
Further animated series began to be released in the 2000s, the first two
of which focused on the prequel trilogy-era Clone Wars.
After Disney's acquisition of Lucasfilm, only The Clone Wars was kept in
the canon of continuity of the episodic Star Wars films.
Two additional half-hour animated series were created: Rebels, which ties into the
original trilogy, and Resistance, which ties into the sequel trilogy.
An additional spin-off series from The Clone Wars, titled
The Bad Batch, debuted on Disney+ in 2021.
Two animated anthology series have been produced: Visions in 2021 and Star Wars Tales, with Tales of
the Jedi in 2022, Tales of the Empire in 2024, and Tales of the Underworld in 2025.
The first young audience animated series, Young Jedi Adventures, set
during the High Republic era, premiered in May 2023.
The first live-action series in the franchise, The Mandalorian, premiered on Disney+ in November 2019 and spawned two spin-offs set
in the same timeframe, The Book of Boba Fett and Ahsoka, as well as another set around the same era, Skeleton Crew.
Additional live-action series include Obi-Wan Kenobi, Andor, and The Acolyte.
The tone is thought_provoking.